<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<pluggable type="plugin" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://schemas.habariproject.org/Pluggable-1.3.xsd">
    <name>HB Audio Player</name>
    <license url="http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0.html">Apache Software License 2.0</license>
	<author url="http://colinseymour.co.uk">Colin Seymour</author>
	<copyright>Copyright 2009</copyright>
	<version>1.1r96</version>
    <url>http://www.lildude.co.uk/projects/hb-audio-player</url>
	<downloadurl>http://www.lildude.co.uk/projects/hb-audio-player</downloadurl>
    <description><![CDATA[HB Audio Player is a highly configurable but simple Flash based MP3 player for Habari.]]></description>
    <guid>4031D1D4-5409-11DE-B1F6-65BE56D89593</guid>
	<help>
		<value><![CDATA[<p>HB Audio Player is a highly configurable but simple mp3 player
                        for all your audio needs. You can customise the player's
                        colour scheme to match your blog theme, have it automatically
                        show track information from the encoded ID3 tags and more.</p>
                        <br>
                        <strong>Basic Usage:</strong><br>
                        <p>The default mechanism for inserting a player in a post is to use the [audio] syntax:<br />

                        <code>[audio:http://www.yourdomain.com/path/to/your_mp3_file.mp3]</code></p>

                        <p>This will insert a player and load your_mp3_file.mp3 into it.</p>

                        <p>Multiple file can be specified by separating their paths/names with commas.</p>

                        <p>You can configure HB Audio Player with a default audio files
                        location so you don’t have to specify the full URL everytime.
                        You can set this location via the Configuration panel. Once set, you
                        can use this syntax:<br>

                        <code>[audio:your_mp3_file.mp3]</code></p>

                        <p>Audio Player will automatically look for the file in your default
                        audio files location. This can be very handy if you decide to move
                        all your audio files to a different location in the future.</p>
                        <br>
                        <strong>Advanced Usage:</strong><br>

                        <p>By default, the player gets the track information from the ID3 tags
                        of the mp3 file, however under some circumstances it won't be able to,
                        for example if the file is on another domain.  This is a
                        <a href="http://www.adobe.com/devnet/flashplayer/articles/cross_domain_policy.html">restriction</a>
                        of the Flash player, but it can be over-ridden.</p>

                        <p>You can however pass the artist and title information when inserting the
                        player using the following syntax:<br>

                        <code>[audio:your_mp3_file.mp3|titles=The title|artists=The artist]</code></p>

                        <p>For multiple files:<br>

                        <code>[audio:mp3_file_1.mp3,mp3_file_2.mp3|titles=Title 1,Title 2|artists=Artist 1,Artist 2]</code></p>
                        ]]></value>
	</help>
</pluggable>
